NGUYỄN PHẠM THIỆN BÌNH

Senior Software Engineer

Day of birth: 16/10/1993

Email: iambinhnpt@gmail.com

Phone: 0909575359

C-902 Jamila Khang Dien apartment building, Phu Huu ward, Thu Duc city, Ho

Chi Minh city

Profile

I have a solid expertise in front end / back end technologies, JS frameworks, architecture design, and strategies to build software from the ground up as well as manage an existing software system, with over 5 years of experience as a software engineer.

Key Skills

Business Domains: CMS - Commerce - eLearning

Languages: HTML - CSS - JS - Typescript

Databases: RDBMS - NoSQL - Blockchain (level knowledge)

Ecosystem: Scrum/Agile - NodeJS/ExpressJS/NestJS - ReactJS/React Native/ NextJS ...

Architectural Patterns: Monolithic/Micro-services/Micro-frontends

WORK EXPERIENCES

11/2021 - present	NOVALAND GROUP
Position:	Senior Software Engineer

- Participate in the development of projects Online Process, Loyalty Program, CMS Portal
- Online Process: maintain and develop additional features for dashboard portal. (FE)
- Loyalty Program: Data flow analysis and interface design support for projects, product optimization (FE)
- CMS Portal: Analyze data flows, design and create the required APIs for the project (BE)
- Write dockerfile and support CI/CD process, release projects to production
- Write test, add and manage performance test tool
- Review code for other members

03/2020 - 11/2021	PROPZY SERVICES COMPANY LIMITED
Position:	Senior Front-end Engineer

- Participating in the development of the Propzy map, investment dashboard project, in charge of the entire frontend segment
- Analyze data flow and manage interface design for projects, product optimization
- Write dockerfile and support CI/CD process, release projects to production
- Write unit test, add and manage performance test tool
- Build and manage npm module
- Review code for other members



06/2018 - 03/2020	Allgrowlabo Co, Ltd.
Position:	Front-end Developer

- Create component in client side with ReactJS/Next
- Create a connection to retrieve data generated from the backend.
- Manage data flow generated between components created at client side

- Create API and handle some tasks on server side using NodeJS and ExpressJS

- Handle html/css/scss/JS/Jquery tasks when required
- Occasionally, create API and handle some tasks on server side using NodeJS and ExpressJS

09/2017 - 06/2018	Allgrowlabo Co, Ltd.	
Position:	Junior Software Developer	
- Design User Interfaces.		
- Writing wordpress, HTML, CSS, JS code for development website		
- Debug code bugs for company's client web project.		
- Testing and Maintaining the Applications developed by Allgrowlabo		

PROJECT

Work project:		
NOVALAND GROUP	CMS Portal: This project aspires to create a unified content management system to manage various types of content from multiple business units that can be created on NovalD, this project analyzes users and their roles. to give them the right permissions for each business unit object. This project uses technologies: NestJS, CASL, ReactJS, Loyalty Program: This project brings the feature to accumulate points for NovalD app users, classifying users into membership classes. The project uses technologies: NestJS, ReactJS, Typescript, Redux, Material UI, Online Process: The project was created to support the Business Development team to process the flow of deposit and reservation papers through the NovalD app to the Portal Admin and synchronize with the company's CRM system. Project using technology: NodeJS, ReactJS, MobX,	

Map Module: Create real estate planning maps module @Propzy/map from scratch by react, typescript, leaflet, rollup, babel. This module is used for other teams to integrate the map application into their project. Map Propzy: Create real estate planning maps with marker, polygon, search, filter, authentication functions. The project is implemented according to the Microfrontend model, using NextJS, leaflet, webpack, PROPZY SERVICES **Appraisal Propzy:** The project aims to automate the steps of real estate **COMPANY LIMITED** appraisal, synthesize data and return the result of the appraisal price, display the price summary table and report the price trend from time to time. The project is made using NextJS, Bootstrap, Webpack, Docker,... Investment Dashboard: This project aims to create a quick list of investmentable real estate products in the form of a list and display on the map. The project is made using NextJS, Bootstrap, Webpack, Docker, Leaflet, React Table... Nanairo Otmo, Sekokan, Osh: The site is built using Laravel + React/Vue/Nuxt with more than 50 child pages, my main job is to create components on the client side. **Daito, Dejicon:** I was tasked with obtaining data from the provided API and processing it using React/WordPress (using PHP). As is the case with Allgrowlabo Co, Ltd. the Daito project, A university child page for an event, it takes data from the provided API of twitter and Instagram tweets, images with specific hashtags and puts images and content on the site. **Litalicojr:** Create an admission page with the necessary forms, the data will be processed and displayed on the admin page, with integrated

Academic project:

registration with twitter and google.

SPA Forum app: Use React to create a SPA Forum App. With key tasks: Build APIs by ExpressJS, Display data from APIs, Validate users and data, Use Redux to process application data

To-do app: built with Create React App, React Redux, and Firebase.

EDUCATION

08/2011 - 06/2016

UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY HCMC

Major: Electronics